Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box 22, Folder (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Earnings and Hours in Blooming Rail, Structural, Plate, and Billet Mills, Iron and Steel Industry 1933 and 1935, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Welfare Work in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Charles Close. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Joseph Germano; Lee Shaw; Elmo Hohman; William Spriegel, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By The Reviewing Stand. Radio discussion. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Earningsand Hours in Blast Furnaces Bessemer Converters, Open-Hearth Furnaces, and Electric Furnaces 1933 and 1935, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Frances Perkis; Isador Lubin. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Collective Bargaining in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By American Iron and Steel Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Collective Bargaining in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Steel and Men, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Harold Hatcher. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Some Problems of the Steel Industry in Pittsburgh, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Benjamin Fairless. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: The Steel Monopoly and Your Job, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Walter Reuther. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Status of the Labor Supply and Training Activities in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Physical Examinations in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Practices Relating to Apprentice Training Programs in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Practices Relating to Vacations with Pay for Wage-Earning Employees in the Iron and Steel Industry for 1941, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Employees Suggestion Programs in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Collective Bargaining in the Steel Industry: 1937, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Fifty Employee-Benefit Plans in the Basic Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Joseph Zisman. Item is in English.
- Box 22, Folder (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Picture Story of Steel, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Charles Wilson's Own Story of Break with Truman, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Steel Labor Case of 1952, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: These are the Facts in the Steel Controversy, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Steel Companies in the Wage Case. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Wage Case, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Industry's View on Who Lost the Steel Strike, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Lessons of the Steel Strike, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Why Does Steel Strike Go on Despite Best Wage Offer in Industry's History?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Study of Federal Seizure of Steel Mills, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By US Congress. Congressional Record. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Facts on the Steel Industry as Viewed by the Press, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Compare Youngston's Offer with the Demands of the Steelworkers' Union, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By The Youngston Sheet and Tube Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Editorial Judgement on the Steel Wage Demands, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Collection of Newsitems on Steel Wage. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Press Fact Sheet on the Steel Case, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Background Memo Wage Trends in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Statement by John A. Stephens, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By John Stephens. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: President Truman Discusses the Steel Crisis, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Harry Truman. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: These are the Facts, Mr. President, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Clarence Randall. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: WSB's Steel Recommendations: " A Shocking Package", Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By John Bane, JR. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Unin Shop?... Yes, But There are Other Major Issues in the Steel Dispute, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: The Truth, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Statement by Benjamin Fairless, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Seizure the New Push-Button Warfare on Business, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: The Steelworkers' Demands are Justified and reasonable, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Collective Bargaining Negotiations and Contracts, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: In the Hands of One Man, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Charles Hook. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Pattern Bargaining and the United Steelworkers, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By George Seltzer. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Preliminary Injuction to Restrain Government from Carrying out Steel Seizure, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Decision by Judge David A. Pine. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Steelworkers and the national Economy, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By David McDonald. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: News ad background Informations, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Labor Relations reporter. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Postwar Wage Determination in the Basic Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Albert Ree. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: The Truth, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 32: The Union's Side in the Steel Crisis, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 33: The Double Standars of Stabilization, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By C. L. Austin. Item is in English.
- Box 22, Folder (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Basic Issues in the Nationwide Steel Strike, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By George Hicks; Conrad Cooper. Radio Interview on the Steel Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Steel Negotiations and You, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By Steel Companies Coordinating Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: It Could Happen Only in the U. S., Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Price and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By Roger Blough. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Information About Forthcoming Negotiations, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By United States Steel Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Memorandum of Agreement Between Basic Steel Companies and United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The Unionization of the American Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By Walter Galenson. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Text of Opinions in Steel Case, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: David McDonald, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: A Talk of Two Towns, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Is the West Making the Grade in the Steel Industry?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By G. Langdon White. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Your Key to the Issues, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Inflation as a Way of Life, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Need for a Wage Increase, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: The 1959 Labor Dispute in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Testimony Before the Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By George Humphrey. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Fact-Finding in the Steel Dispute, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By Public Relations Department, United Steelworkers of America. he Meaning of the Mitchell Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Statistics Bearing on the Steel Dispute, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By James Mitchell. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Economic Summary in Support of 1959 Wage policy, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Case for Higher Wges, Full Employment and Better working Conditions in the Steel Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Importance of Steel Prices in Consumer Price Index, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: More Steel and More Jobs, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Facts on Steel: Profits, Productivity, Prices and Wages, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Steel Management and the Acceptance of Unionism, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By Byron Parry. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Letter Concerning Negotiations with the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Why a Steel Price Increase in 1957?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: A Review of the Iron and Steel Industry in the United States, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By American iron and Steel Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: The Kaiser Solution is the Wiser Solution, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By David McDonald; Edgar Kaiser. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Steel Prices, Profits, Productivity and wages, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: Statistics Breating on the Steel Dispute, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By james Mitchell. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Occupational Wage Differentials in the Basic Steel Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By Jack Stieber. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Steel and the National Economy, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 32: An Economic Documentation of the Steelworkers' Position in the 1959 Steel Strike, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 33: Where the Steel Companies Stand, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By The Steel Companies Coordinating Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: What comes after Steel Strikes, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Box 22, Folder (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Social Security in Wartime and After, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By Recommendations by 68 of the Nation's Leading Experts. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Social Insurance, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By Frank Huddle. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Right to Survey, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: What Will Social Security Mean to You?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By William J. Matteson. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Financing Old-Age, Survivors, and Disaility Insurance, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By Advisory Council on Social Security Financing. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Security and Dignity in an Expanding Economy, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Social Security in the United States, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By Mary Ross. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Paying for the Social Services, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By R. H. S Crossman. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bibliography on Collective Bargaining in the Human Services, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By Institute of Labor and Indutrial relations. Item is in English.
- Box 22, Folder (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Letter Outlining the Society's Projects, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
    By William Overman; Wayne Grover; Henry Edmunds. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Plan List of Labor Records, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)